from pr_2_basic import Question

questions: list[Question] = [
    {
        "question": "What module enables runtime type checking in Python?",
        "answer": "typing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What data structure uses key-value pairs?",
        "answer": "dict"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword exits a loop early?",
        "answer": "break"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword is used to handle exceptions?",
        "answer": "try"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword checks object identity?",
        "answer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which built-in function returns an iterator over pairs of index and value?",
        "answer": "enumerate"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which special method is called when an object is created?",
        "answer": "__init__"
    },
    {
        "question": "What keyword is used to define an anonymous function?",
        "answer": "lambda"
    },
    {
        "question": "What keyword is used to define a context manager?",
        "answer": "with"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which keyword creates a generator function?",
        "answer": "yield"
    },
]